George Gaylord Simpson Papers 1918-1984 Mss.Ms.Coll.31
American Philosophical Society
- George Gaylord Simpson Papers
  - Series I. Correspondence, 1925-1984; 36 linear feet (Box 1-73)
    - Sherborn, C. Davies, n.d. (Box 59)
    - Sherman, Michael Ian, 1967 (Box 59)
      State University of New York--Stoney Brook
    - Sherwood, George H., 1927-35 (Box 59)
      Director AMNH
    - Shevyreva, N.S., 1977, 80, 82 (Box 59)
    - Shew, Demetria M., 1978 (Box 59)
    - Shifflett, Howard, 1973 (Box 59)
    - Shigehara, Nobuo, 1978 (Box 59)
    - Shimada, Izumi, 1976 (Box 59)
    - Shiomoto, Marian, 1966 (Box 59)
    - Shoben, Edward Joseph Jr., 1960 (Box 59)
    - Shopping International, Inc., 1970, 74 (Box 59)
    - Shor, Elizabeth N., 1977 (Box 59)
    - Short, Charles L., 1970 (Box 59)
    - Shoshani, Jeheskel, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Shotwell, J. Arnold, 1961, 65 (Box 59)
    - Shotwell, Thomas K., 1966 (Box 59)
    - Showstead, Richard A., n.d. (Box 59)
    - Shrock, Robert R., 1941-42 (Box 59)
    - Shuey, Philip McG., 1938 (Box 59)
    - Shulson, James Richard, 1966 (Box 59)
    - Shute, Evan V., 1960 (Box 59)
    - Shutts, C.F., 1962-63 (Box 59)
    - Sibley, Charles G., 1962, 69 (Box 60)
    - Sickenberg, Otto, 1935 (Box 60)
    - Siemers, Charles T., 1974 (Box 60)
    - Siever, Raymond, 1968 (Box 60)
    - Sige, Bernard, 1973, 79, 83 (Box 60)
      Palaeovertebrata
    - Signeux, J., 1965 (Box 60)
    - Sigogneau, Mlle D., 1970 (Box 60)
    - Silberberg, Bob, 1964 (Box 60)
    - Silberling, Albert C., 1932-36, 37-42, 45 (Box 60)
    - Silberling, Robert W., 1945, 48, 60, 63, 84 (Box 60)
      Siblerling's father
    - Silberman, Miles, 1971 (Box 60)
    - Siler, Leon M., 1971 (Box 60)
    - Sill, William D., 1982-83 (Box 60)
    - Sillman, Leonard R., 1957-58, 62 (Box 60)
      origin of vertebrates
    - Sills, David L., 1963 (Box 60)
      International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences
    - Silver, Caswell, 1950 (Box 60)
    - Silverman, Edith R., 1966 (Box 60)
    - Silverman, Madge, 1975 (Box 60)
    - Silverstein, Alvin, 1969-70 (Box 60)
    - Silvestri, L.G., 1963 (Box 60)
    - Simmons, Perez, 1932 (Box 60)
    - Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1956, 70 (Box 60)
    - Simons, Elwyn L., 1959-62, 64-66, 68-71 (Box 60)
    - Simpson, Beryl B., 1973, 76 (Box 60)
    - Simpson, Elizabeth L., 1977, 80 (Box 60)
      daughter
    - Simpson, George G., 1962, n.d (Box 60)
    - Simpson, Helen A., 1934 (Box 60)
    - Simpson, Helen Frances, 1931, 39 (Box 60)
    - Simpson, Joan, 1965 (Box 60)
    - Simpson, Larry C., 1972 (Box 60)
      no relation
    - Simpson, Leon M., 1971 (Box 60)
    - Simpson, Lester C., 1966 (Box 60)
    - Simpson, Martha, 1928, 31, 33 (Box 60)
      Sister
    - Simpson, Ruth DeEtte, 1959 (Box 60)
    - Sims, Ripley S., 1963 (Box 60)
    - Simson, George K., 1964 (Box 60)
    - Sinclair, Mary, 1974 (Box 60)
    - Sinclair, N.L., 1928-29 (Box 60)
    - Singer, Barry F., 1971 (Box 60)
    - Singer, Marcus, 1968 (Box 60)
    - Singer, Ronald, 1961-78 (Box 60)
    - Singleton, W. Ralph, 1961 (Box 60)
    - Siniff, L.S., 1932 (Box 60)
    - Sinnott, Edmund W., 1949, 53 (Box 60)
    - Sinsheimer, Robert L., 1973, 78 (Box 60)
      PNAS
    - Sitaraman, Kalavathy, 1970 (Box 60)
    - Sitzmann, Gerhard H., 1977 (Box 60)
    - Six, Ray L., 1943 (Box 60)
    - Skeel, Elinor E., 1967 (Box 60)
      Biological Sciences Honor Society
    - Skidmore College, 1963-64 (Box 60)
    - Skinner, Brian J., 1970 (Box 60)
    - Skinner, William R., 1982 (Box 60)
    - Sklar, Jeffrey, 1970 (Box 60)
      Haverford College
    - Skorkowski, Edward, 1958-59, 64 (Box 60)
    - Sladen, William J.L., 1960 (Box 60)
    - Slater, A.E., 1964 (Box 60)
    - Slater, J.A., 1974 (Box 60)
    - Slattery, Martin O., 1980 (Box 60)
    - Slaughter, Bob H., 1960, 63, 68, 74, 78, 82 (Box 60)
      Photo and manuscript
    - Sleigh, Nick, 1976 (Box 60)
    - Slijper, E.J., 1949 (Box 60)
    - Sliter, William V., 1979 (Box 60)
      USGS, P&S branch
    - Sloan, Alfred P., Jr., 1959 (Box 60)
    - Sloan, Robert E., 1962, 70, 72 (Box 60)
    - Slocum, Lyn, 1975 (Box 60)
    - Slone, Ralph W., 1951 (Box 60)
    - Slud, M.H., 1963 (Box 60)
    - Small, James, 1946-47 (Box 61)
    - Smiley, J.R., 1968 (Box 61)
      Univ. of Colorado--Boulder, President
    - Smiley, Terah L., 1959-60, 67-68, 74-75 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Barbara L., 1982 (Box 61)
    - Smith, David L., 1981-82, 84 (Box 61)
      World Good News Network
    - Smith, Ella Thea, 1952, 57 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Emil L., 1964 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Fred P., 1968 (Box 61)
      Hawaiian Mission Children's Society
    - Smith, G. Elliott, 1931 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Gary, 1972 (Box 61)
    - Smith, H.T.U., 1940 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Henry Lee, Jr., 1940 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Hobart M., 1930, 47, 49, 53-54, 60-61, 65 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Homer P., 1954 (Box 61)
      Edwin Grant Conklin Memorial Fund
    - Smith, Homer W., 1950, 52-53, 60 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Jill, 1984 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Lester W., 1940-42 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Lucy Cranwell, 1970-71 (Box 61)
    - Smith, M.S., 1960 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Myron Bement, 1933 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Peter I., 1982 (Box 61)
      Open Earth
    - Smith, Robert L., 1973 (Box 61)
    - Smith, T.L., 1966 (Box 61)
      Epperson v. Arkansas and Scopes v. Tennessee
    - Smith, Vincent E., 1960, 63 (Box 61)
    - Smith, Warren Allen, 1956 (Box 61)
      Humanism
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1926, 46, 50, 59, 65 (Box 61)
      Smithsonia
    - Smithsonian Institution (Committee on Future Policies), 1946-47; 2 folders (Box 61)
    - Smithsonian Institution (Office of Fellowships and Grants), 1981 (Box 61)
    - Smithsonian Institution (Press), 1983 (Box 61)
    - Smolker, Rosemary G., 1966, 71, 77-78 (Box 61)
    - Smyth, Fred H., 1930-31, 33, 37, 39 (Box 61)
    - Sneath, P.H.A., 1961, 63-64 (Box 61)
    - Sneed, Jan, 1958 (Box 61)
    - Snell, Foster D., Inc., 1955 (Box 61)
      loyalty oath
    - Snow, Joel Alan, 1967 (Box 61)
    - Snyder, Laurence H., 1951 (Box 61)
    - Snyder, Lorraine, 1958 (Box 61)
    - Snyder, Ted, 1937 (Box 61)
    - Social Problems (journal), 1967 (Box 61)
    - Social Security Administration, 1980 (Box 61)
    - Sociedad Cientifica Argentina, 1948, 70, 74-75, 78 (Box 61)
    - Societe Geologique de France, 1957 (Box 61)
    - Societe Royale Les Naturalistes de Mons et du Borinage, 1956 (Box 61)
    - Societe de Chimie Industrielle, Inc. (American Section), not dated (Box 61)
    - Society for Animal Protective Legislation, 1959 (Box 61)
    - Society for Social Responsibility in Science, 1957, 61 (Box 61)
    - Society for Visiting Scientists, 1948, 50 (Box 61)
    - Society for the Investigation of the Unexplained, 1968-69 (Box 61)
    - Society for the Study of Evolution, 1946-49, 56-74 (Box 61)
    - Society for the Study of Evolution (Conference on the Evolution of Behavior), 1953-57, 67 (Box 61)
    - Society of American Bacteriologists, 1926 (Box 61)
    - Society of Fellows, 1966 (Box 61)
    - Society of Sigma Xi, 1944-45, 48-54, 57, 63, 69 (Box 62)
    - Society of Systematic Zoology, 1951-79 (Box 62)
    - Society of Vertebrate Paleontology, 1957-59, 66, 69-70 (Box 62)
    - Society of Vertebrate Paleontology (Cenozoic Committee), 1959, 65-66 (Box 62)
    - Society of Vertebrate Paleontology (Constitution revision), 1957-58 (Box 62)
    - Soergel, W., 1935 (Box 62)
    - Sogandares, Franklin, 1962 (Box 62)
    - Sojka, Gary, 1979 (Box 62)
    - Sokal, Robert R., 1956, 63 (Box 62)
    - Sokaski, Michael, 1960 (Box 62)
    - Sokolov, I.I., 1954 (Box 62)
    - Sokolov, V., 1974-77 (Box 62)
    - Sollas, W.J., 1927 (Box 62)
    - Somervell, Brehon, 1936 (Box 62)
    - Somoza, B.A., 1940 (Box 62)
    - Somppi, Lynn, 1975 (Box 62)
    - Sondaar, Paul Y., 1972 (Box 62)
    - Sonneborn, T.M., 1949, 77 (Box 62)
    - Soper, Ellis Clarke, 1952, 54 (Box 62)
    - Sorenson, Denis S., 1957 (Box 62)
    - Soria, Miguel F., 1980-83 (Box 62)
    - Soto, Roberto Sarmiento, 1947 (Box 62)
    - Soule, Augustus W., 1967-68 (Box 62)
    - South African Museum (Cape Town), 1976, 78-79 (Box 62)
    - South African National Foundation for the Conservation of Costal Birds, 1972 (Box 62)
    - South Australian Museum, 1956-57 (Box 62)
    - South Dakota, State University of, 1958 (Box 62)
    - South, Dudley P., 1941 (Box 62)
    - Southern Illinois University, 1958 (Box 62)
    - Southern Methodist University, 1954 (Box 62)
    - Southwood, T.R.E., 1981 (Box 62)
    - Souza, Antonio Jose Alves de, 1946 (Box 62)
      PanAmerican Congress of Mining/Engineering/Geology
    - Spalletti, L.A., 1979 (Box 63)
    - Sparck, R., 1952 (Box 63)
    - Sparrow, A.H., 1979 (Box 63)
    - Spector, N. Herbert, 1964 (Box 63)
    - Spencer, Edgar W., 1960 (Box 63)
    - Spencer, Frank, 1980 (Box 63)
    - Spencer, Judy L., 1983 (Box 63)
    - Spieker, Edmund M., 1946, 57, 67 (Box 63)
    - Spiess, Eliot B., 1976 (Box 63)
      Evolution editor
    - Spieth, Herman T., 1956 (Box 63)
    - Spivack, Morris J., 1954 (Box 63)
    - Spongberg, Barbara, 1971 (Box 63)
    - Sprague, James M., 1945 (Box 63)
    - Squire, Morris B., 1971 (Box 63)
    - Squires, Donald F., 1959 (Box 63)
    - Stachowiak, E.J., 1969 (Box 63)
    - Staff, Virgil C., 1960 (Box 63)
      Creationist geologists
    - Stagner, Wilbur L., 1941 (Box 63)
    - Stamps, Walter, 1966 (Box 63)
    - Standard Oil Company, 1936 (Box 63)
    - Stanford Univeristy, 1959 (Box 63)
    - Stanley, Meredith, 1968-69 (Box 63)
    - Stanley, Steven M., 1971, 75 (Box 63)
    - Stanton, Betty, 1982-83 (Box 63)
      MIT Press
    - Staples, John H., 1979 (Box 63)
    - Staples, Laurence C., 1937, 39 (Box 63)
      All Soul's Church
    - Starck, D., 1966 (Box 63)
    - Statler Hotel, 1956 (Box 63)
    - Stead, Anita, 1957 (Box 63)
    - Stearns, Harold T., 1944, 63 (Box 63)
    - Stebbins, G. Ledyard, Jr., 1948-1973; 56.0 Item(s) (Box 63)
      Biographical and personal data; Colbert, Edwin A.; Conferences and symposia; Editorial matters; Evolution; Genetics; Genetics of plants; Lectures, public speaking; Paleontology; Physiology; Poetry and literature; Political issues; Publication; Publication -- Evolution; Publication -- Science; Recommendations; Referee's report; Research support; Society for the Study of Evolution; Travel -- Algeria; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
    - Stecher, Robert M., 1960, 70 (Box 63)
    - Stechert, G.E. and Company, 1925-26, 34 (Box 63)
    - Steck, Roger, 1966 (Box 63)
      Dickinson College
    - Steedman, Eline Viault, 1927-28, 36 (Box 63)
    - Steel, Rhoda Knight, 1956 (Box 63)
    - Steffan, A.W., 1975 (Box 63)
      Entomologica Germanica
    - Steffey, Sandra, 1975 (Box 63)
    - Stehli, Francis G., 1955, 65 (Box 63)
    - Steidtmann, James R., 1978 (Box 63)
    - Stein, Horst, 1972 (Box 63)
    - Stein, M. Russell, 1935 (Box 63)
    - Steinbock, Ted, 1980-82 (Box 63)
    - Steiner, Gerolf, 1963 (Box 63)
    - Steiner, Robert A., 1981 (Box 63)
    - Steinmayer, R.A., 1949 (Box 63)
    - Steklis, Horst D., 1974-75 (Box 63)
    - Stensio, Erik A., 1928, 33, 35, 69-70 (Box 63)
    - Stenzel, H.B., 1949-51, 74 (Box 63)
    - Stephens, T.C., 1942 (Box 63)
    - Stephenson, Robert C., 1960 (Box 63)
      American Geological Institute
    - Stern Brothers, 1956 (Box 63)
    - Stern, Bernhard J., 1950 (Box 63)
    - Sternberg, Charles M., 1925-29, 39, 41 (Box 63)
    - Sternberg, Charles W., 1942 (Box 63)
    - Sternberg, George F., 1950 (Box 63)
    - Sternberg, R.M., 1936 (Box 63)
    - Sternberg, Vernon, 1972-73 (Box 63)
      Southern Illinois University Press
    - Stetter, Rick, 1978 (Box 63)
    - Stevcic, Zdravko, 1972, 73, 82 (Box 63)
    - Stevenson, Blanche, 1979 (Box 63)
    - Stevenson, J.A., 1940 (Box 63)
    - Steward, Julian H., 1946, 61 (Box 63)
      American Anthropological Association
    - Stewart, Bruce, 1941, 52, 67 (Box 63)
    - Stewart, Herbert H., 1961 (Box 63)
    - Stewart, Roy P., 1934 (Box 63)
    - Stewart, T.D., 1959 (Box 63)
    - Stiles, Lois, 1978 (Box 63)
    - Stiles, William, 1959 (Box 63)
    - Stipanicic, Pedro N., 1970-71 (Box 63)
    - Stirton, R. A. (Ruben Arthur), 1930-1964; 77.0 Item(s) (Box 63)
      Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Evolution -- Horses; Fellowships, assistantships; National Research Council; Paleontology; Requests for aid in finding positions; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; University of California, Berkeley; Zoology; Zoology -- Classification; Zoology -- Nomenclature
    - Stock, Chester (Dr. and Mrs.), 1941-42, 46-47, 51 (Box 63)
    - Stocking, Marion K., 1963 (Box 63)
    - Stoddard, Carl K., 1941 (Box 63)
    - Stoermer, Monika, 1981 (Box 63)
    - Stone, E.L., 1926 (Box 63)
    - Stonehouse, Bernard, 1969-74, 76 (Box 63)
    - Stoppani, A.O.M., 1970 (Box 63)
    - Storer, Robert W., 1957 (Box 64)
    - Storer, Tracy I., 1949, 63 (Box 64)
    - Storr, G.M., 1959 (Box 64)
    - Storrs, Eleanor E., 1979-81 (Box 64)
    - Stout, Thompson Mylan, 1947, 49-50 (Box 64)
    - Stoutamire, Steve, 1973 (Box 64)
    - Stovall, J. Willis, 1928, 37, 48 (Box 64)
    - Stowe, Bruce B., 1961 (Box 64)
    - Stowell, Robert, 1969 (Box 64)
    - Strahan, Ronald, 1961-62 (Box 64)
    - Strahler, Arthur N., 1970 (Box 64)
    - Strand, A.L., 1964 (Box 64)
    - Stratyner, Max, 1958 (Box 64)
    - Straus, William L., Jr., 1959, 62 (Box 64)
    - Strauss, Bernard S., 1954 (Box 64)
    - Strohm, Paul, 1979 (Box 64)
    - Stromer, Ernst, 1926, 30-31 (Box 64)
    - Strong, Edward W., 1963 (Box 64)
    - Strong, William M., 1932 (Box 64)
    - Stubblefield, C.J., 1947 (Box 64)
      International Paleontological Union
    - Studia Entomologica (journal), 1963 (Box 64)
      Principles of Animal Taxonomy critique
    - Stuessy, Tod F., 1977 (Box 64)
    - Stugren, Bogdan, 1969 (Box 64)
    - Stump, John P., 1960 (Box 64)
    - Stunkard, Horace W., 1957 (Box 64)
    - Stunt, A.V., 1972, 75-78 (Box 64)
    - Sturgeon, Myron T., 1946 (Box 64)
    - Sturm, Marjorie K., 1967-70 (Box 64)
    - Stussi, Fritz, 1961 (Box 64)
    - Sudre, Jean, 1980 (Box 64)
    - Sues, Hans-Dieter, 1979 (Box 64)
    - Sullivan, J. Magruder, 1941 (Box 64)
    - Sun, Ai-Lin, 1979 (Box 64)
    - Sunderland, Florence E., 1961-62 (Box 64)
    - Sunline Agencies, 1973 (Box 64)
    - Surendra, Dr., 1973 (Box 64)
    - Sussex, Ian, 1976 (Box 64)
    - Sutcliffe, Anthony, 1968, 70-71, 79 (Box 64)
      Tea cloth
    - Sutcliffe, Robert, 1959 (Box 64)
    - Suthard, James A. and Marie, 1962, 64 (Box 64)
    - Sutherland, P.K., 1982 (Box 64)
    - Sutt, Toomas, 1970-80 (Box 64)
    - Sutton, John F., 1971 (Box 64)
    - Svec, Petr, 1978, 83 (Box 64)
    - Swan, Emery F., 1954-55 (Box 64)
    - Swanepoel, Pierre, 1979-80 (Box 64)
    - Sweeney, Leo, 1964 (Box 64)
    - Sweet Briar College, 1957 (Box 64)
    - Sweet and Maxwell, Ltd., 1950 (Box 64)
    - Sweet, S.R., 1937 (Box 64)
    - Swinton, W.E., 1929, 32, 37 (Box 64)
    - Sylvester-Bradley, P.C., 1954, 60-61 (Box 64)
    - Syracuse University, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Systematics Association, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Szalay, Frederick, 1974-77, 79-80 (Box 64)
    - Szebenyi, n.d. (Box 64)
    - Szlapelis, Casimiro, 1933, 70 (Box 64)
    - Szwykowski, Jan, 1965-66 (Box 64)
    - Taber, Richard D., 1980 (Box 64)
    - Taborsky, George, 1977 (Box 64)
    - Tagert, D.G., 1936 (Box 64)
    - Tagliacozzo, Giorgio, 1963, 66 (Box 64)
    - Tahir, Sherif, 1967 (Box 64)
    - Takai, Fuyuji, 1937, 78 (Box 64)
    - Taketomo, Yasuhiko, 1962 (Box 64)
    - Talbot, S.A., 1962 (Box 64)
    - Tanensche, W., 1932, 34 (Box 64)
    - Tankersley, Garvin E. (Mrs.), 1975 (Box 64)
    - Tanner, George, 1977 (Box 64)
    - Tanner, James, 1969 (Box 64)
    - Tapia, 1933 (Box 64)
    - Tappen, Donald Putnam, 1940-42 (Box 64)
    - Taquet, Philippe, 1973, 75 (Box 64)
    - Tarasoff, F.J., 1968 (Box 64)
    - Taratsidis, Desi., 1971 (Box 64)
    - Tarka, Chester S., 1966-67, 69 (Box 64)
    - Tarling, D.H., 1971 (Box 64)
    - Tarlo, L.B.H., 1967 (Box 64)
    - Tassy, Pascal, 1982 (Box 64)
    - Tate, G.H.H., 1935, 39 (Box 64)
    - Tavris, Jay, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Tax, Sol, 1953, 74 (Box 64)
      American Anthropologist
    - Taylor, Calvin W., 1979 (Box 64)
    - Taylor, Charles J., 1953 (Box 64)
    - Taylor, Dwight, 1958 (Box 64)
    - Taylor, Hugh, 1967 (Box 64)
    - Taylor, J.R., 1957 (Box 64)
    - Taylor, Peter, 1971 (Box 64)
    - Taylor, Thomas N., 1977 (Box 64)
    - Taylor, Walter F., 1949 (Box 64)
    - Teachers College, 1936 (Box 64)
    - Teal, John J., 1957 (Box 64)
    - Tedford, Richard H., 1967, 70, 73-74, 79, 81-82 (Box 64)
    - Teeri, James A., 1981 (Box 64)
    - Teichert, Curt, 1941-42, 52, 65 (Box 64)
    - Teilhard de Chardin, Pere, 1936, 41 (Box 64)
    - Teisseire, Augusto, 1934-35 (Box 64)
    - Teissier, Georges, 1947-48, 65 (Box 64)
    - Teleki, Geza, Jr., 1966 (Box 65)
    - Temple University, 1952 (Box 65)
    - Tennessee, University of, 1959 (Box 65)
    - Ternes, Alan, 1973, 75 (Box 65)
      Natural History
    - Terra, Helmut de, 1979 (Box 65)
      Also under De Terra, Helmut
    - Tetry, A., 1966 (Box 65)
    - Tewari, B.S., 1970 (Box 65)
    - Texas, University of (Austin), 1953 (Box 65)
    - Thaler, Louis, 1967-68, 82 (Box 65)
    - Thatcher, Bruce K., 1974 (Box 65)
      Human footprints in Mesozoic
    - Thayer, Shirley, 1960 (Box 65)
    - Thenius, Erich, 1959, 60-62, 70, 79, 82 (Box 65)
    - Thiel, George A., 1959 (Box 65)
    - Thieme, Frederick P., 1969 (Box 65)
    - Thieme, W.J. amd Cie, 1949 (Box 65)
    - Thiriot, Richard V., 1953 (Box 65)
    - Thom, W.T., Jr., 1929 (Box 65)
    - Thomas, Charles C., 1928-30 (Box 65)
      Publisher
    - Thomas, D.W., 1951 (Box 65)
    - Thomas, Dana Lee, 1955 (Box 65)
    - Thomas, David J., 1978 (Box 65)
      Kamarskoto monograph
    - Thomas, G.A., 1968-69 (Box 65)
      Beaumaris area geology
    - Thomas, Joseph C., 1963 (Box 65)
    - Thomas, Margaret C., 1941, 65-66 (Box 65)
    - Thomas, Roger D.K., 1978 (Box 65)
    - Thomas, V.R., 1953 (Box 65)
      utopia
    - Thomas, W. Stephen, 1940 (Box 65)
    - Thomel, G., 1972-73 (Box 65)
    - Thompson, James B., Jr., 1972 (Box 65)
    - Thompson, James F., 1976, 78-79 (Box 65)
    - Thompson, Norm, 1975 (Box 65)
    - Thompson, Raymond H., 1941-42, 67, 79 (Box 65)
    - Thomson, Albert, 1938, 40 (Box 65)
    - Thomson, Keith S., 1964, 83 (Box 65)
      Yale University Commencement
    - Thomson, Wilburt, 1948 (Box 65)
    - Thone, Frank, 1935, 40 (Box 65)
      Science Service
    - Thorington, Richard W., Jr., 1966-69 (Box 65)
    - Thornton, A., 1965 (Box 65)
    - Thornton, I.W.B., 1968 (Box 65)
    - Thornton, John F., 1980-81, 83 (Box 65)
      Washington Sqare Press
    - Thorogood, Elizabeth, 1977 (Box 65)
    - Thorpe, Malcolm R., 1924, 27 (Box 65)
    - Tiegs, E.W., 1926 (Box 65)
    - Tieje, A. J. (Artus J.), [Jerry], 1922-1941; 30.0 Item(s) (Box 65)
      Biographical and personal data; Lectures, public speaking; Paleontology; Publication; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Zoology
    - Tiffany, L. Hanford, 1954-55, 59 (Box 65)
    - Tillson, David S., 1965, 69 (Box 65)
    - Tilney, A.G., 1970-72, 74-75 (Box 65)
    - Time (magazine), 1946 (Box 65)
    - Time Reading Program, 1964-65, 68 (Box 65)
      Attending Marvels reprint
    - Tinbergen, N., 1972 (Box 65)
    - Tindale, Norman B., 1952 (Box 65)
    - Ting, Su-yin, 1979-81, 83 (Box 65)
    - Tintant, Henri, 1964, 82 (Box 65)
    - Tipler, Frank J., 1982-83 (Box 65)
    - Tipton, Vernon J., 1964 (Box 65)
    - Tobey, William H., 1960 (Box 65)
    - Tobia, Phillip V., 1965, 71, 73, 76 (Box 65)
    - Tobien, Heinz, 1954, 79 (Box 65)
    - Todd, Cyril, 1971 (Box 65)
    - Toerien, M.J., 1953 (Box 65)
    - Toft, Ronald, 1966 (Box 65)
    - Tolbert, Bert M., 1971-72 (Box 65)
    - Toledo, Laura A., 1982 (Box 65)
    - Tomida, Yukimitsu, 1981-82, 84 (Box 65)
    - Tomlinson, W. Harold, 1927 (Box 65)
    - Tonni, Eduardo P., 1971 (Box 65)
    - Toohey, Loren H., 1947, 53, 59, 78 (Box 65)
    - Toots, Heinrich, 1971 (Box 65)
      Climatic Control of Holartic Mammal Interchanges
    - Torennaga, S., 1932-35 (Box 65)
    - Toronto, University of, 1948, 55 (Box 65)
    - Torpin, Richard, 1971, 74-75 (Box 65)
    - Torres, Luis Maria, 1930 (Box 65)
    - Torrey, Theodore W., 1960 (Box 65)
    - Toulmin, Stephen, 1964, 65 (Box 65)
    - Towe, Arnold L., 1965 (Box 65)
    - Towe, Kenneth M., 1978 (Box 65)
    - Townsend, J. Ives, 1959 (Box 65)
    - Trask, Parker D., 1946 (Box 65)
    - Traub, Hamilton, 1964 (Box 65)
    - Traub, Robert, 1965-66, 68, 70, 73, 75 (Box 65)
    - Travis, Arnold (Mrs.), 1974 (Box 65)
    - Travis, Janet L., 1970-71, 73 (Box 65)
    - Trembley, F.J., 1950, 64, 66-67 (Box 66)
    - Trever, James E., 1973 (Box 66)
    - Triarch Productions Ltd., 1971-72 (Box 66)
    - Trivers, Robert, 1981 (Box 66)
    - Trofimov, Boris A., 1975, 82 (Box 66)
    - Troost, Cornelius, 1966 (Box 66)
    - Troost, Neil J., 1965-66 (Box 66)
    - Troxell, Edward L., n.d. (Box 66)
    - Trumbull, Richard, 1978 (Box 66)
      American Institute for Biological Sciences
    - Truyols Santonja, Jaime, 1960-61, 84 (Box 66)
      Also under Truyols, Jaime
    - Tsai, B., 1926 (Box 66)
    - Tsubura, Fumihiro, 1981-82 (Box 66)
      Science (Kagaku) editor
    - Tubingen, Universitat, 1981 (Box 66)
    - Tuck, A. David, 1963 (Box 66)
    - Tucuman, Universidad Nacional de, 1974 (Box 66)
    - Tui, Co, 1947 (Box 66)
    - Tulane Studies in Zoology (journal), 1961 (Box 66)
    - Tupper and Love, Inc., 1963-65 (Box 66)
    - Tupper, Jane, 1968-69 (Box 66)
    - Turgel, Gordon, 1949, 51 (Box 66)
    - Turnbull, William D., 1958, 67-68, 70, 72-75, 80-81 (Box 66)
    - Turner, Raymond M., 1975 (Box 66)
    - Tuttle, Russell H., 1981 (Box 66)
    - Tuve, Merle, 1970 (Box 66)
      NAS Daniel Giraud Elliot Fund
    - Twenhofel, William H., 1931 (Box 66)
    - Twentieth Century Authors, 1952 (Box 66)
    - Tyler, Ralph W., 1957 (Box 66)
    - Tyler, Ruth, 1967-68, 84 (Box 66)
    - Uberman, Nancy, 1979 (Box 66)
      The Dial Pree
    - Udall, Morris K. (U.S. House of Representatives), 1968 (Box 66)
    - Udvardy, Miklos D.F., 1959, 64-68, 71 (Box 66)
    - Uexkull, G. v., 1960 (Box 66)
    - Uitgeverij Mouton and Company, 1972 (Box 66)
    - Ulmer, Roland, 1979 (Box 66)
    - UNESCO, 1951, 63-64 (Box 66)
      Biological Aspects of Race, 64
    - Unicorn Press, Inc. Unidentified Correspondents, 1969 (Box 66)
    - Union College, 1958 (Box 66)
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, Embassy, 1977 (Box 66)
    - United States. Department of Commerce (Bureau of the Census), 1978 (Box 66)
    - United States. Department of Commerce (National Technical Information Service), 1977 (Box 66)
    - United States. Department of Justice (Office of the Attorney General), 1966 (Box 66)
    - United States Geological Survey (Advisory Committee Correspondence), 1953-65, 79 (Box 66)
    - United States Geological Survey (Advisory Committee Meeting), 1955 (Box 66)
      Agenda material
    - United States Geological Survey (Advisory Committee, statements from Divisions), 1957 (Box 67)
    - United States Geological Survey (Director, speeches), 1956, 58 (Box 67)
      Reports
    - United States Geological Survey (Estimate of Appropriations, FY61), 1961 (Box 67)
    - United States Geological Survey (Estimate of Appropriations, FY65), 1965 (Box 67)
    - United States Geological Survey (Management Improvement Report), 1954 (Box 67)
    - United States Geological Survey (Miscellany), 1931-32, 35-36 (Box 67)
    - United States Geological Survey (Policies and Plans of the Geological Survey), 1950 (Box 67)
    - United States Geological Survey (Preventing Conflicts of Interest), 1963 (Box 67)
    - United States Geological Survey (Publication Catalogs), 1959-60, 62, 65-66 (Box 67)